<resources>
    <string name="app_name">Garcia_Labexer4</string>

    <string-array name="cName">
        <item>ICBC</item>
        <item>JPMorgan Chase</item>
        <item>China Construction Banks</item>
        <item>Agricultaural Bank of China</item>
        <item>Bank of America</item>
        <item>Apple</item>
        <item>Ping An Insurance Group</item>
        <item>Bank of China</item>
        <item>Royal Dutch Shell</item>
        <item>Wells Fargo</item>
        <item>Exxon Mobil</item>
        <item>AT&amp;T</item>
        <item>Samsung Electronics</item>
        <item>Citigroup</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cCountry">
        <item>China</item>
        <item>United States</item>
        <item>China</item>
        <item>China</item>
        <item>United States</item>
        <item>United States</item>
        <item>China</item>
        <item>China</item>
        <item>Netherlands</item>
        <item>United States</item>
        <item>United States</item>
        <item>United States</item>
        <item>South Korea</item>
        <item>United States</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cIndustry">
        <item>Major Banks</item>
        <item>Major Banks</item>
        <item>Major Banks</item>
        <item>Regional Banks</item>
        <item>Major Banks</item>
        <item>Computer Hardware</item>
        <item>Diversified Insurance</item>
        <item>Major Banks</item>
        <item>Oil &amp; Gas Operations</item>
        <item>Major Banks</item>
        <item>Oil &amp; Gas Operations</item>
        <item>Telecommunications Services</item>
        <item>Semiconductors</item>
        <item>Major Banks</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cCeo">
        <item>Shu GU</item>
        <item>Jamie Dimon</item>
        <item>Wang Zuji</item>
        <item>Huan Zhao</item>
        <item>Brian T. Moynihan</item>
        <item>Tim Cook</item>
        <item>Ma Mingzhe</item>
        <item>Chen Siqing</item>
        <item>Bernadus Cornelis Magriiet van Beurden</item>
        <item>Timothy Allen Sloan</item>
        <item>Darren W. Woods</item>
        <item>Randall L. Stephenson</item>
        <item>Hyun-Suk Kim</item>
        <item>Michael L. Corbat</item>
    </string-array>

    <string-array name="cMess">
        <item>Industrial &amp; Commercial Bank of China Ltd. engages in the provision of commercial banking and financial services. </item>
        <item>JPMorgan Chase &amp; Co. is a financial holding company, which provides financial and investment banking services.</item>
        <item>China Construction Bank Corp. engages in the provision of financial and banking services.</item>
        <item>Agricultural Bank of China engages in the provision of international commercial banking and financial services.</item>
        <item>Bank of America Corp. is a bank and financial holding company, which engages in the provision of banking and nonbank financial services.</item>
        <item>Apple, Inc. engages in the design, manufacture, and marketing of mobile communication, media devices, personal computers, and portable digital music players.</item>
        <item>Ping An Insurance (Group) Co. of China Ltd. engages in the provision of financial products and services.</item>
        <item>Bank of China Ltd. engages in the provision of banking and related financial services such as commercial and investment banking, and insurance and investment services.</item>
        <item>Royal Dutch Shell Plc engages in the oil and natural gas production. It operates through three segments: Upstream, Downstream, and Corporate.</item>
        <item>Wells Fargo &amp; Co. is a bank holding company that engages in the provision of banking, insurance, investments, mortgage, and consumer and commercial finance.</item>
        <item>Exxon Mobil Corp. engages in the exploration, development, and distribution of oil, gas, and petroleum products.</item>
        <item>AT&amp;T, Inc. is a holding company, which engages in the provision of telecommunications and digital entertainment services.</item>
        <item>Samsung Electronics Co., Ltd. engages in the manufacturing and selling of electronics and computer peripherals.</item>
        <item>Citigroup, Inc. is a global financial services holding company specializes in banking and financial solutions.</item>
    </string-array>

</resources>
